{
    "id": "a5c2b11154c34cf186f71a7b687f8a50",
    "title": "Active And Passive Verbs Exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "366e3a6d31e34d54b781916557bf078e",
            "title": "Active And Passive Voice Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "The letters ................................ in the morning.",
                    "description": "A passive verb is required here because the subject is not the doer of the action. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "posted",
                        "have posted",
                        "were posted"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "She .................................... of our decision.",
                    "description": "A passive verb is required here because the subject is not the doer of the action. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "has informed",
                        "informed",
                        "has been informed"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The old man .................................... alone for many years.",
                    "description": "Either the present perfect or the present perfect continuous tense is possible here.",
                    "answers": [
                        "has been living",
                        "has been lived",
                        "has lived"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "His kind words ................................ me.",
                    "description": "An active verb is required here because the subject is the doer of action. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "were encouraged",
                        "encouraged",
                        "were being encouraging"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I .................................... by his kind words.",
                    "description": "A passive verb is required here because the subject is not the doer of the action. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "encouraged",
                        "was encouraged",
                        "was encouraging"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He .................................... everything in detail.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "explained",
                        "was explained",
                        "has been explained"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Everything ................................. in detail.",
                    "description": "A passive verb is required here because the subject is not the doer of the action. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "explained",
                        "was explained",
                        "has explained"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She ................................. him instantly.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "recognized",
                        "has been recognized",
                        "was recognized"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He ...................................",
                    "description": "A passive verb is required here because the subject is not the doer of the action. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "instantly deported",
                        "has instantly deported",
                        "was instantly deported"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I .................................. unawares.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "caught",
                        "was caught",
                        "have caught"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She ................................ into the room happily.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "danced",
                        "was danced",
                        "has danced"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She ................................ aback.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "took",
                        "was taken",
                        "has taken"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}